foontastic.com 2014-04-03

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site www.foontastic.com. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring pages, computer platform, date/time, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userнs computer tied to information about the user. Our site does not use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following advertising companies: Google Adsense, AzoogleAds, Valueclick. Please check their websites for respective privacy policy documents.

Advertising

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [ http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml](http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your Internet Security software. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

External Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Contact  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:
